<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home on Dongdong Zhu</title>
    <link>//localhost:4321/</link>
    <description>Recent content in home on Dongdong Zhu</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:4321/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/vitae/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;Education&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;09/2023 ~ 06/2025, Research Master, Department of Communication Science, ASCoR, University of Amsterdam&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;09/2018 ~ 11/2019, Master of Science, Department of Media and Communications, London School of Economics and Political Science&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;09/2014 ~ 06/2018, Bachelor of Arts, School of Journalism, Renmin University of China&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;09/2016 ~ 01/2017, Exchange Student, College of Communication, National Chengchi University&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;conference-paper&#34;&gt;Conference Paper&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[1] &lt;strong&gt;Zhu, D.&lt;/strong&gt; (2024, June 23). &lt;em&gt;Are Housewives Getting Depressed? A Machine Learning Study Based on YouTube&lt;/em&gt;. 74th International Communication Association Regional Hub, Beijing, China. &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/housewives&#34;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/CeciliaZhu1997/mycode/blob/main/Housewife_data_collection.ipynb?short_path=b32dc21&#34;&gt;[dataset]&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/CeciliaZhu1997/mycode/blob/main/Housewife_data_analysis.ipynb&#34;&gt;[code]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;work-in-progress&#34;&gt;Work in Progress&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[2] Strycharz, J., Möller, M., Ho, J., &lt;strong&gt;Zhu, D.&lt;/strong&gt;, Huo, Q. &lt;em&gt;Developing a Comparative Media Dataset from Web Crawl Data for Communication Science Research.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[3] Wirz, D., Schäfer, S., Schneider, F., &lt;strong&gt;Zhu, D.&lt;/strong&gt;, Tan, Y. &lt;em&gt;TikTok News and the Illusion of Knowledge: Effects of Thematic Framing and Emotionalization.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;industry-publications&#34;&gt;Industry Publications&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/Articles&#34;&gt;Media Analysis: Articles Published on News Platforms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;research-experience&#34;&gt;Research Experience&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2024.05 ~ 2024.12, Research assistant, Amsterdam School of Communication Research (ASCoR), Supervised by &lt;a href=&#34;https://scholar.google.com/citations?hl=nl&amp;amp;user=JV-KAo4AAAAJ&#34;&gt;Joanna Strycharz&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://scholar.google.com/citations?hl=en&amp;amp;user=EukNVL0AAAAJ&amp;amp;view_op=list_works&amp;amp;sortby=pubdate&#34;&gt;Justin Ho&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=rKWov8wAAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en&#34;&gt;Marthe Möller&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup&gt;[2]&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2024.03 ~ 2024.12, Research assistant, Amsterdam School of Communication Research (ASCoR), Supervised by &lt;a href=&#34;https://scholar.google.com/citations?hl=de&amp;amp;user=Z1uaZaEAAAAJ&amp;amp;view_op=list_works&amp;amp;sortby=pubdate&#34;&gt;Dominique Wirz&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://scholar.google.com/citations?hl=en&amp;amp;user=ev269g0AAAAJ&amp;amp;view_op=list_works&amp;amp;sortby=pubdate&#34;&gt;Frank Schneider&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=r48_ZVMAAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en&#34;&gt;Svenja Schäfer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup&gt;[3]&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/research&#34;&gt;More&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;working-experience&#34;&gt;Working Experience&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2023.02 ~ 2023.06, Operation Specialist, Department of Operation, DoraHacks, Remote&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2020.03 ~ 2023.02, Marketing Specialist, Department of Global Marketing, Xiaomi, Beijing, China&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2017.11 ~ 2020.03, Freelancer, Platform and Content Group, Tencent, Remote&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2019.06 ~ 2019.09, Intern, The Chinese Weekly, Kylin Prime Group, London, the UK&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2017.05 ~ 2017.08, Intern, MSL China, Publicis Groupe, Beijing, China&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2017.02 ~ 2017.05, Intern, China Central Television, Beijing, China&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;honor--awards&#34;&gt;Honor &amp;amp; Awards&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;National Encouragement Scholarship, Ministry of Education of China (1/22), 2017&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Outstanding Student Leader Award, Renmin University of China, 2017&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Second Prize, Undergraduate Research Foundation, Renmin University of China, 2017&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Excellent Works Prize, AD Campus Spring Competition of China, 2017&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Third Prize of Scholarship, Renmin University of China, 2016&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Outstanding Student Leader Award, Renmin University of China, 2016&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;National Encouragement Scholarship, Ministry of Education of China (1/22), 2015&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Housewives Getting Depressed? A Machine Learning Study Based on YouTube</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/housewives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/housewives/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This paper was accepted by the 74th International Communication Association (ICA) Regional Hub Beijing.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This study aims to explore housewives’ digital expression based on 1800 videos from YouTube using a supervised machine learning approach.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Major Depressive Disorder (MDD) has symptoms including feeling depressed or sad, loss of interest, etc., lasting at least two weeks, according to the American Psychiatric Association. It is considered the leading cause of &amp;ldquo;disease-related disability&amp;rdquo; among females according to the World Health Organization’s Global Burden of Disease, with females being at 1.5 to 3 times higher risk than males (Kessler, 2003).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Diving Online? Mapping Algorithmic Cospirituality on TikTok</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/conspirituality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/conspirituality/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This research was a group project from the Digital Methods Initiative Summer School 2023 at the University of Amsterdam.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.digitalmethods.net/Dmi/TheDivineOnline&#34;&gt;Full Project Report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Conspirituality is a politico-spiritual philosophy from Ward and Voas (2011) which draws attention towards the idea that individuals interested in spirituality and alternative belief systems exhibit flexibility towards traditional belief systems or organizational structures and privilege alternative, even deviant or stigmatized, claims to truth. These individuals, therefore, run the risk of entertaining or promoting various conspiracy theories online. Our project examines this phenomenon within the context of algorithm-dominated platforms (i.e. TikTok) to further understand how people come to know their own social, political, and religious/spiritual realities. Further, the dynamic of humanalgorithm relations introduces an additional layer of complexity in the formation of ideas related to algorithms. This curiosity can be best described by the idea of algorithmic conspirituality which brings together ideas related to faith in algorithms, spirituality, and conspiracy (Cotter et al., 2022).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolution by Other Memes: Online Subcultures, Modular Ideologies and the Political Compass</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/memes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/memes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This paper was a group project from the Digital Methods Initiative Summer School 2023 at the University of Amsterdam.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.digitalmethods.net/pub/Dmi/SummerSchool2023/Revolution%20By%20Other%20Memes-Project%20Report%E2%80%93%20DMSS2023.pdf&#34;&gt;Full Project Report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;individual-work&#34;&gt;Individual Work&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Created in 2017, r/PoliticalCompassMemes grew in popularity in 2020 as a space to classify political ideologies by locating all manner of phenomena - from the welfare state to Wojak avatars - on the political compass image macro. The memes address political style instead of political substance, treating issues and events as occasions to recalibrate the compass. Our analysis yielded four main findings: 1) &amp;lsquo;meta&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;based&amp;quot; memes that give insight into group identity and interplay between groups, 2) how symbols, public figures, and signs are remixed and utilized to build identity within the subreddit at large and within the political categories, and 3) how issue spaces provide insight into a politics of (memetic and stylistic) participation rather than serious political engagement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep Life Rolling, Keep Life Running!</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/poprun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/poprun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi POP Run is a highly successful domestic marketing campaign that has been held several times in China, encouraging users to adopt healthy lifestyles.  In 2021, during the height of the COVID-19 pandemic and lockdown restrictions, I spearheaded a virtual run contest to promote exercise and well-being at home. This online event garnered impressive global participation, attracting over 27,000 users over a three-week period. Building on this success, we organized smaller-scale offline POP Run events in 2022, which were also well-received.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Smart Living a Reality for Everyone!</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/renovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/renovation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I led a very meaningful project during my three-year work experience at Xiaomi. The project involved using Xiaomi Smart AIoT products to renovate the homes of brand users for free who were in need.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The participants in this project include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A poor but lovely family from the Philippines. The elder daughter registered for the event and asked if we could provide her with a better study environment and reduce her mother&amp;rsquo;s burden.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A couple from Vietnam who adopted several children and are seeking better living environments for the kids.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A doctor from Italy who contributed significantly during the pandemic and wishes to have a relaxing home environment for himself and his mother.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My role in this project was as follows:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Day We Celebrated the New Year 24 Times!</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/newyears/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/newyears/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a very special campaign as it is my first time working independently as a project manager, just six months into my first full-time job. We completed a global marketing event &amp;ndash; inviting our users from every time zone in the world to celebrate New Year together!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The campaign, titled Xiaomi POP - 24 New Years, hosted a 24-hour livestream starting from New Zealand, where the time is the earliest (GMT+12) and has the very first New Year worldwide, and ended at Aitutaki, one of the Cook Islands in the South Pacific (GMT-10), the last time zone globally. From each time zone, we invited one individual or a group of brand users (actual users, not actors) to join the livestream and record their moments as the new year arrived. A total of 34 cities and 102 users from around the world participated, and the livestream ultimately garnered over 102 million impressions and 2 million clicks.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:4321/images/24newyears.png&#34; alt=&#34;cities participating in the livestreaming&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Analysis Articles that I Published from 2017 to 2020</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/articles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I started working as a freelancer for Tencent, one of the biggest Internet companies in China, from 2017 to 2020. My main job was to write articles related to the latest domestic and global social media trends and news consumption. Over the three years, I wrote over 300,000 Chinese characters and received a total readership of over 2.5 million, with many articles reposted by influential media outlets nationwide.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the article links (in Chinese):&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Females, Male Homosexuality and Gender Hegemony: A Critical Discourse Analysis of Boys&#39; Love Novels in the Chinese Context</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/lse_thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/lse_thesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This research was my graduate thesis (Merit) from the Department of Media and Communications at the London School of Economics and Political Science.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a growing trend in China where Boys&amp;rsquo; Love novels, featuring romantic stories between gay men, are experiencing significant popularity among female readers. However, these novels also face ongoing regulations by authorities. Issues of gender and homosexuality have been a topic of discussion for over ten decades, with close connections to power and hegemony.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Innovation in Writing of We-Media Accounts: A Case Study of the Jiang Ge Tokyo Murder Trial</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/ruc_thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/ruc_thesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This research was my undergraduate thesis (Distinction) from the School of Journalism at the Renmin University of China.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In November 2017, the murder case of Jiang Ge, a Chinese female student studying in Japan, garnered long-term attention on Chinese social media platforms. We-Media, particularly WeChat subscription accounts, played a significant role in capturing public attention, setting the agenda for discussions, and disseminating information during the trial. This paper aims to explore how We-Media writing skills have innovated and developed, using the depictions of the Jiang Ge murder case from WeChat subscription accounts as a case study.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo Ivy</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Hugo theme was ported from &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dmulholland/ivy&#34;&gt;Ivy&lt;/a&gt;, a minimalist website generator built in Python. I don&amp;rsquo;t have time to document this theme. You have to read the source code to understand what it can do. All I can say for now is that I love it. It is clean, minimal, and responsive.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I hope you will enjoy this theme. The source code is &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/yihui/hugo-ivy&#34;&gt;on Github&lt;/a&gt;. Happy hacking!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Achievements</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/career/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/career/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en-us&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;head&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta charset=&#34;utf-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;title&gt;Marketing Achievements&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;meta property=&#34;og:title&#34; content=&#34;Marketing Achievements&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;twitter:card&#34; content=&#34;summary&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta property=&#34;description&#34; content=&#34;A summary of marketing projects led by Dongdong, featuring online challenges, smart living solutions, global livestreams, and media analysis.&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta property=&#34;og:description&#34; content=&#34;Marketing achievements by Dongdong Zhu, including digital campaigns, media analysis, and global celebrations.&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;link href=&#34;//localhost:4321/experiences/index.xml&#34; rel=&#34;alternate&#34; type=&#34;application/rss+xml&#34; title=&#34;Dongdong Zhu&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;//localhost:4321/css/style.css&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;//localhost:4321/css/fonts.css&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;style type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;&#xA;      .experience-container {&#xA;        display: flex;&#xA;        align-items: center;&#xA;        margin-bottom: 20px;&#xA;      }&#xA;      .logo {&#xA;        flex: 1;&#xA;        max-width: 150px;&#xA;        margin-right: 20px;&#xA;      }&#xA;      .logo img {&#xA;        width: 150px; /* 保证图片宽度一致 */&#xA;        height: auto;&#xA;      }&#xA;      .text {&#xA;        flex: 3;&#xA;        text-align: left;&#xA;      }&#xA;      /* 增加列表样式的小圆点符号 */&#xA;      .experience-container ul {&#xA;        list-style-type: disc;&#xA;        margin-left: 20px;&#xA;      }&#xA;    &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;body class=&#34;Projects&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;section id=&#34;career&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &#xA;      &lt;!-- 职业经历 1 --&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;experience-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;logo&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;img src=&#34;./24newyears.png&#34; alt=&#34;Career Logo 3&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;&#xA;              &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/newyears&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Streamed New Year’s Across 24 Timezones in One Livestream: First-Ever Global Celebration&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &#xA;      &lt;!-- 职业经历 2 --&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;experience-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;logo&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;img src=&#34;./poprun.png&#34; alt=&#34;Career Logo 1&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;&#xA;              &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/poprun&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Led Successful Online Challenge: 27,000 Participants Embraced Daily Running&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;      &lt;!-- 职业经历--&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;experience-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;logo&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;img src=&#34;./renovation.png&#34; alt=&#34;Career Logo 2&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;&#xA;              &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/renovation&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Empowered Families in Need Through Free Smart Living Solutions &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;      &lt;!-- 职业经历--&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;experience-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;logo&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;img src=&#34;./article.png&#34; alt=&#34;Career Logo 4&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;&#xA;              &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/Articles&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Media Analysis Articles that I Published from 2017 to 2020&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/section&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/body&gt;&#xA;&lt;/html&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research Projects</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/research/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en-us&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;head&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta charset=&#34;utf-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;title&gt;Research Projects&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;meta property=&#34;og:title&#34; content=&#34;Research Projects&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;twitter:card&#34; content=&#34;summary&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta property=&#34;description&#34; content=&#34;Research Collaborations and Experiences&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta property=&#34;og:description&#34; content=&#34;Research Collaborations and Experiences&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;link href=&#34;//localhost:4321/experiences/index.xml&#34; rel=&#34;alternate&#34; type=&#34;application/rss+xml&#34; title=&#34;Dongdong Zhu&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;//localhost:4321/css/style.css&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;//localhost:4321/css/fonts.css&#34; /&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;style type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;&#xA;      .experience-container {&#xA;        display: flex;&#xA;        align-items: center;&#xA;        margin-bottom: 20px;&#xA;      }&#xA;      .logo {&#xA;        flex: 1;&#xA;        max-width: 150px;&#xA;        margin-right: 20px;&#xA;      }&#xA;      .logo img {&#xA;        width: 150px; /* 设置图片宽度一致 */&#xA;        height: auto;&#xA;      }&#xA;      .text {&#xA;        flex: 3;&#xA;        text-align: left;&#xA;      }&#xA;      /* 增加小圆点符号 */&#xA;      .experience-container p {&#xA;        list-style-type: disc;&#xA;        margin-left: 20px;&#xA;      }&#xA;    &lt;/style&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;body class=&#34;Projects&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;section id=&#34;research-python&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2&gt;Using Python&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;      &#xA;&lt;!-- 研究经历 --&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;experience-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;logo&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;./housewives.png&#34; alt=&#34;Research Logo 1&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;      &lt;li&gt;&#xA;        06/2024, Conference, &lt;em&gt;Are Housewives Getting Depressed? A Machine Learning Study Based on YouTube&lt;/em&gt;, 74th International Communication Association (ICA) Regional Hub, Beijing, China.&#xA;        &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/housewives&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt; &#xA;        &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/CeciliaZhu1997/mycode/blob/main/Housewife_data_collection.ipynb?short_path=b32dc21&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[dataset]&lt;/a&gt; &#xA;        &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/CeciliaZhu1997/mycode/blob/main/Housewife_data_analysis.ipynb&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[code]&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;      &#xA;&lt;!-- 研究经历--&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;experience-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;logo&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;./schipol.png&#34; alt=&#34;Research Logo 1&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;      &lt;li&gt;05/2024, Coursework, &lt;em&gt;Data Retrieval and Analysis Based on API at Schiphol Airport&lt;/em&gt;, Big Data and Automated Content Analysis, University of Amsterdam &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/CeciliaZhu1997/mycode/blob/main/Schipol.ipynb&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[code]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;!-- 研究经历 2 --&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;experience-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;logo&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;./compasses.png&#34; alt=&#34;Research Logo 2&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;      &lt;li&gt;07/2023, Workshop, &lt;em&gt;Revolution By Other Memes: Online Subcultures, Modular Ideologies And The Political Compass&lt;/em&gt;, Digital Methods Initiative Summer School, University of Amsterdam&#xA;        &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/files/Revolution_by_other_memes_link.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[poster]&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/memes&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;      &lt;!-- 研究经历 3 --&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;experience-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;logo&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;img src=&#34;./spiritural.png&#34; alt=&#34;Research Logo 3&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;07/2023, Workshop, &lt;em&gt;The Divine Online? Mapping Algorithmic Conspirituality on TikTok&lt;/em&gt;, Digital Methods Initiative Summer School, University of Amsterdam &#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/files/TheDivineOnline_Poster.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[poster]&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/conspirituality&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/section&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;section id=&#34;research-r&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2&gt;Using R&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;experience-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;logo&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;img src=&#34;./alcohol.png&#34; alt=&#34;Research Logo 4&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;01/2024, Group coursework, &lt;em&gt;Visualization of University Students&#39; Alcohol Use, Snack Consumption, and Sports Participation&lt;/em&gt;, Using R for Data Wrangling, Analysis and Visualization, University of Amsterdam &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/files/r_group/Group2_final.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[report]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;section id=&#34;research-qualitative&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2&gt;Qualitative Studies&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;experience-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;08/2019, Thesis, &lt;em&gt;Females, Male Homosexuality and Gender Hegemony: A Qualitative Analysis of Boy’s Love Novels in the Chinese Context&lt;/em&gt;, Department of Media and Communications, London School of Economics and Political Science &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/lse_thesis&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[abstract]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;experience-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;06/2018, Thesis, &lt;em&gt;Innovation in Discourse Writing of We-Media Accounts: Taking the Jiang Ge Tokyo Murder Case as an Example&lt;/em&gt;, School of Journalism, Renmin University of China &lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:4321/ruc_thesis&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[abstract]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;section id=&#34;research-undergraduate&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2&gt;Social Practice&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;experience-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;          &lt;li&gt;2017.11, Report, &lt;em&gt;Innovation in Communicating Public Information with New Media - a Case Study of the Yinchuan Government&lt;/em&gt;, Undergraduate Research Foundation, Renmin University of China&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;/body&gt;&#xA;&lt;/html&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
