<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Career on Dongdong Zhu</title>
    <link>//localhost:4321/tags/career/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Career on Dongdong Zhu</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:4321/tags/career/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[Campaign] Keep Life Rolling, Keep Life Running!</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/poprun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/poprun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi POP Run is a highly successful domestic marketing campaign that has been held several times in China, encouraging users to adopt healthy lifestyles.  In 2021, during the height of the COVID-19 pandemic and lockdown restrictions, I spearheaded a virtual run contest to promote exercise and well-being at home. This online event garnered impressive global participation, attracting over 27,000 users over a three-week period. Building on this success, we organized smaller-scale offline POP Run events in 2022, which were also well-received.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Campaign] Make Smart Living a Reality for Everyone!</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/renovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/renovation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I led a very meaningful project during my three-year work experience at Xiaomi. The project involved using Xiaomi Smart AIoT products to renovate the homes of brand users for free who were in need.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The participants in this project include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A poor but lovely family from the Philippines. The elder daughter registered for the event and asked if we could provide her with a better study environment and reduce her mother&amp;rsquo;s burden.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A couple from Vietnam who adopted several children and are seeking better living environments for the kids.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A doctor from Italy who contributed significantly during the pandemic and wishes to have a relaxing home environment for himself and his mother.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My role in this project was as follows:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Campaign] The Day We Celebrated the New Year 24 Times!</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/newyears/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/newyears/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a very special campaign as it is my first time working independently as a project manager, just six months into my first full-time job. We completed a global marketing event &amp;ndash; inviting our users from every time zone in the world to celebrate New Year together!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Introduction&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;The campaign, titled Xiaomi POP - 24 New Years, hosted a 24-hour livestream starting from New Zealand, where the time is the earliest (GMT+12) and has the very first New Year worldwide, and ended at Aitutaki, one of the Cook Islands in the South Pacific (GMT-10), the last time zone globally. From each time zone, we invited one individual or a group of brand users (actual users, not actors) to join the livestream and record their moments as the new year arrived. A total of 34 cities and 102 users from around the world participated, and the livestream ultimately garnered over 102 million impressions and 2 million clicks.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;![cities participating in the livestreaming](/images/24newyears/cities_participating_in_the_livestreaming.png)&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;My Responsibilities&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;Of course, this was a very challenging campaign for the project manager, but also inspiring, especially for someone who just started her career. I began preparing for this project in October 2020, and over the next two months, I completed the following tasks:&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creative Planning&lt;/strong&gt;: Developed activity ideas and planned event content, such as 24-hour live stream materials, promotional plans, and product promotion strategies during the event.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Activity Execution&lt;/strong&gt;: Coordinated project compliance applications to ensure global implementation; built the live stream webpage; created promotional content for various social platforms; set up offline event venues for live stream recording; produced and sent event-related gifts to participating users.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Management&lt;/strong&gt;: Led a team of 10, collaborating with Xiaomi&amp;rsquo;s 14 regional market teams, legal department, development department, and 18 other teams to ensure the smooth execution of the event.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the thing I am most proud of: finding 102 brand users who were willing to join us!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Publications] Media Analysis Articles that I Published from 2017 to 2020</title>
      <link>//localhost:4321/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:4321/articles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I started working as a freelancer for Tencent, one of the biggest Internet companies in China, from 2017 to 2020. My main job was to write articles related to the latest domestic and global social media trends and news consumption. Over the three years, I wrote over 300,000 Chinese characters and received a total readership of over 2.5 million, with many articles reposted by influential media outlets nationwide.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the article links (in Chinese):&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
